Guide to the Rice University Information Files, 1910-2019 UA 361
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: D
  - Dac - Net
  - Daichman, Graciela S.
  - Dalai Lama
  - Damanik, David
  - Dameron, Kenneth
  - [Rice] Dance Theatre
  - Daniel, Price
  - Daniell, P.J.
  - Dankberg, Mark
  - [Pals'] Darki-Arts
  - Data Science Initiative
  - Dating Violence Project
  - Daughters of the American Revolution (DAR), Rice Members
  - Davenport, Kimberly
  - Davidson, Chandler
  - Davidson, Joe
  - Davies, Joseph I.
  - Davis, Jack
  - Davis, Joe
  - Davis, Kathleen A.
  - Davis, Mark E. Delos Reyes
  - Davis, Sam H.
  - Dawe, Grosvenor
  - Dead Sea Scroll Conference
  - Dead Week
  - Dean, Alice C.
  - Dean of Undergraduate Education
  - Dean of Women
  - Deans, Harry A.
  - Dean's List of Superior Students
  - Dean's Summit
  - Dearmond, Carolyn
  - Debate Club/Team
  - Debre, Olivier
  - DeBremaecker, Jean Claude
  - de Carvalho, Carlos D.
  - Decennial Celebration, December 1, 1922
  - Deegan, John Jr.
  - Deem, Michael
  - Dees, Morris
  - de Figueiredo, Rui J.P.
  - Degrees
  - Deigaard, William
  - DeKooning, Elaine
  - Del Conte, Chris
  - [Rice] Delivery Services
  - DeLorenzo, Mauro
  - Delphian Society
  - de Martinez, Maria Teresa
  - de Menil, Dominique
  - de Menil, John
  - [Rice] Democratic Caucus
  - Democratic Convention, 1928
  - Dennis, John E.
  - Departments - New
  - Derrick, Wayne
  - Derrida, Jacques
  - Dershowitz, Alan
  - [Rice] Desegregation
  - [Rice] Design Fete
  - DesRoches, Reginald
  - Dessler, Alexander J. (2 Folders)
  - de Vecsey, Esther
  - [Rice] Development Office
  - Development Studies
  - D'Evelyn, Mark P.
  - Devine, Carolyn
  - deVries, Hugo
  - Dewey, Dr. John
  - DeWitt, Cape Gassner
  - Dharan, Bala G.
  - Diamant, N.S.
  - Dickens, Gerald
  - Diehl, Michael
  - Dietz, Elizabeth
  - Digital Library Initiative at Rice
  - Digital Signal Processing
  - Digitization [School] for Culture Heritage Professionals
  - Dignitaries and Personalities on Campus
  - Dini, Richard F.
  - "Dining in Hall"
  - Diplomas - Vault Collection
  - Disability Resource Center
  - Disciplinary Records
  - [The] Discussion Group
  - [Rice] Discussion groups
  - Distinguished Chairs Dinner
  - Distribution Requirements
  - Ditman, Mark [Food and Housing]
  - [Rice University] Division of University Advancement
  - Dix, Robert
  - Dix, William S.
  - Djerejian, Edward P.
  - Dobbins, Stella
  - Dodd, William E.
  - Dodds, Stanley A.
  - Doerr Institute for New Leaders
  - Doerr, John
  - Doherty, Robert Pace
    See also: Board [of Governors, of Trustees]
  - Dole, Elizabeth
  - Doody, Terrence
  - Doran, Charles
  - Doty, James Robert
  - Doty, Mark
  - Doughtie, Edward
  - Dove, Kent E.
  - Dowden, Wilfred S. (Dr. and Mrs.)
  - Draft
  - Dressel, Linda L.
  - Dressler, Mylene
  - Drew, Katherine F.
  - Drezek, Rebekah
  - Driscoll, Tom
  - Driskill, Linda
  - Droxler, Andre Willy
  - Drouilhet, Sidney J.
    See also: Flag Case
  - Drugs
  - DSP Leadership Univ. Program [Digital Signing Process]
  - Dual Degree Program
  - Dubay, Brenda Joyce
  - Dubos, Rene
  - Duck, Ian
  - Duggan, Ben H.
  - Duke, Reese D.
  - Dumas, Elva Kalb
  - Dumble, E.T.
  - Duncan, Charles W., Jr.
  - Duncan College
  - [Anne and Charles] Duncan Hall (2 Folders)
  - Dunham, Jane
  - Dunlap, Rhodes
  - Dunne, Edward
  - Dunning, Barry F.
  - Duno-Gottberg, Luis
  - Duplicate Bridge Club
  - Dupre, Dallas D.
  - Dupree, Edmund M.
  - Duran, Juan Garcia
  - Durrani, Ahmad J.
  - Dvoretzky, Edward
  - Dvoretzky, Isaac
  - Dworkin, Steven
  - Dwyer, Charles Arthur
  - Dye, Kenneth W.
  - Dyer, Eddie
  - Dyson, Derek C.
- Series V: E
  - Eaker, Helen
  - Early Decision Admission Plan
  - Earth Science, Dept. of
  - Earth Tub
  - Earth Week (1971)
  - [Rice] Earthquake Simulator
  - Ecklund, Elaine H.
  - Ecological Survival, [Rice] Society for
  - Ecology and Evolutionary Biology
  - Economics, Department of
  - Eddy, Sherwood
  - [Rice] Education Dept.
  - Educational Outreach
  - Educational Technology and Research Assessment Cooperative (ETRAC)
  - Edwards, Edgar O.
  - Edwards, George
  - Edwards, L.P.
  - Edwards, W.F.
  - Edythe Bates Old Recital Hall & Grand Organ
  - Eggers, Mitchell
  - Eggert, Allen
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D.
  - Eisenman, Nicole
  - Eisner, Elmer
  - Elam, Tony
  - Elder Periodical Room [Fondren Library]
  - [Student] Election Ballots, 1933-43
  - Election Center
  - [Student] Elections
  - Electrical and Computer Engineering, Dept. of
  - Electrical Engineering, Dept. of
  - [Campus] Electric Service
  - Electronics Resource Center
  - El-Gamal, Mahmoud A.
  - Elkhouri, Roger
  - Elkins, James A.
  - Ellemann-Jensen, UFFE
  - [Mary Alice] Elliot Loan fund
  - Ellis, William T.
  - Embree, Mark
  - Embry, Lloyd
  - Emergency Preparedness and Recovery Workshop for Librarians and Archivists
  - Emergency Room
  - Emerson, Michael
  - Emison, Sam S.
  - Emma (mule)
  - Emmett, Ed
  - Employee Activity Committee
  - Employee Assistance Program
    See also: United Behavioral Health
  - [Rice] Employer Trip Reduction Program
  - [Student] Employment
  - EMS ([Rice] Emergency Medical Services)
  - Endowed Chairs
  - [Rice] Endowment
  - Energy and Environment Initiative
  - Energy and Environmental Systems Institute
  - Energy Research and Education Foundation
  - "Engaging Houston"
  - Engel, Paul S.
  - Engelhardt, Tristram Jr.
  - Engineering (2 Folders)
  - Engineering Alumni Awards
  - [Rice/TSU] Engineering, Dual Degree Program in
    See also: Dual Degree Program
  - Engineering Design and Development Institute
  - Engineering Education, Society for the Promotion of
  - Engineering, Management and Defense Training Certificate
  - [Rice] Engineering Show
    Photograph: J. A. Fuller
  - Engineering Shows, no. 1-5
  - Engineering Shows, no. 5-14
  - Engineering Society
  - Engineers Without Borders
  - [Rice] English as a Second Language Tutoring Program (ESL)
  - English, Department of
  - English Entrance and Spelling Examinations
  - Ensor, Katherine Bennett
  - Entrance Gates
  - [Rice U.] Environmental Club
  - [Rice] Environmental Conference
  - [Rice U.] Environmental Health and Safety Dept.
  - Environmental Science and Engineering
  - Envision Grants
  - Epsom Downs
  - Equal Employment Opportunity
    See also: Affirmative Action
  - Erfurth, Augie
  - Ernst, Max
  - Eschenbach, Christoph
  - Eska, Chris
  - Esperanto Club
  - Esperanza
  - Esther
  - Ethics in Medicine and Technology, Conference in
  - Eubank J. Thomas
  - Eubank, Nancy Moore (Mrs. John Thomas)
  - Eubanks, Robert
  - Eury, Robert "Bob"
  - Evans, Elinor
  - Evans, Griffith Conrad
  - Evans, John B.
  - Evans, J.W.
  - [An] Evening for Rice's Honor
  - [W. Maurice] Ewing Professorship in Oceanography
  - Ewing, William Maurice
  - Examinations, Final
  - Exchange Programs
  - Exposition of Engineering, Sciences and Arts
  - External Affairs Division
  - [Rice] Extra Point Club
- Series VI: F
  - Facilities and Engineering
  - Factual Sketch
  - Faculty
  - Faculty - Appointments, Promotions, Resignations
  - Faculty - Awards, Fellowships, Grants
  - Faculty Club Board
  - Faculty Forum
  - Faculty Governance & Participation
  - Faculty Handbook
  - Faculty Senate
  - Failor, Ella Marye
  - Fain, Michael L.
  - Falconer, Sir Robert
  - Families, Society of
  - Families Weekend
  - "Family Connections"
  - [Rice] Family issues
  - Farach-Carson, Cindy
  - Farb, Aubrey
  - Farenthold, Frances
  - [William Stamps] Farish Fund
  - Farish Gallery
  - Farish, Libbie Rice
  - Farish, William Stamps
  - Farnsworth, David E.
  - Farnsworth Pavillion.
  - Farrar, R.M.
  - Farrell, Michele L.
  - Farren, Paul
  - Favrot, Laurence H.
  - Favrot Professorship in French
  - [Student and Others] Fees
  - Fellowships - Fulbright
  - Fellowships - National Science Foundation
  - Fellowships - Woodrow Wilson
  - Feminist Economics
  - [Rice Inst.] Fence
  - Fencing
  - Fendley, Francis T.
  - Festive Shirt Day
  - Feustel, Edward A.
  - Few, Arthur A.
  - Fiedler, Leslie A.
  - [Old] Field House
  - Field, Michael
  - [Rice] Film
  - [Rice] Film Productions (Movies, Videos, Commercials, etc. on Campus)
  - [Rice] Film Society
  - Finances
  - Financial Aid
  - Fine Arts, Department of
    See also: Art and Art History, Dept. of
  - Fine Arts Showcase
  - [Anne Smith] Fine Chair in Judaic Studies
  - Finer, Judith
  - Fire Safety Evacuation Plan for Residential Colleges
  - Fischer, Michael M.J.
  - Fischer, Frank M., Jr.
  - [Rice] Fitness Program
    See also: Wellness Program
  - [Rice] Flag
  - Flag Case
  - Flagg, Robert (Bob)
  - Fleming, Jeff
  - Fleming, Lamar
  - Fleming, Renee
  - Fliegel, Raphael N.
  - [Campus] Floods
  - Flux
  - [Rice Inst.] Flying Club
  - Flying Owls
  - Follies
  - Fondren, Ella Cochran
  - Fondren family
  - Fondren Library
  - Fondren, Walter W.
  - [Rice] Food Service (2 folders)
  - Football (Freshmen)
  - Football (General)
  - Football, 1912/13
  - Football, 1913/14
  - Football, 1914/15
  - Football, 1915/16
  - Football, 1916/17
  - Football, 1917/18
  - Football, 1918/19
  - Football, 1919/20
  - Football, 1920/21
  - Football, 1921/22
  - Football, 1922/23
  - Football, 1923/24
  - Football, 1924/25
  - Football, 1925/26
  - Football, 1926/27
  - Football, 1927/28
  - Football, 1928/29
  - Football, 1929/30
  - Football, 1930/31
  - Football, 1931/32
  - Football, 1932/33
  - Football, 1933/34
  - Football, 1934/35
  - Football, 1935/36
  - Football, 1936/37
  - Football, 1937/38
  - Football, 1938/39
  - Football, 1939/40
  - Football, 1940/41
  - Football, 1941/42
  - Football, 1942/43
  - Football, 1943/44
  - Football, 1944/45
  - Football, 1945/46
  - Football, 1946/47
  - Football, 1947/48
  - Football, 1948/49
  - Football, 1950/51
  - Football, 1951/52
  - Football, 1952/53
  - Football, 1953/54
  - Football, 1954/55
  - Football, 1955/56
  - Football, 1957/58
  - Football, 1960/61
  - Football, 1961/62
  - Football, 1962/63
  - Football
  - Football, 1964/65
  - Football, 1965/66
  - Football, 1966/67
  - Football, 1967/68
  - Football, 1968/69
  - Football, 1970/71
  - Football, 1971/72
  - Football, 1973/74
  - Football, 1974/75
  - Football, 1975/76
  - Football, 1977/78 - 1978/79
  - Football, 1979/80
  - Football, 1982/83
  - Football, 1983/84
  - Football, 1985/86
  - Football, 1989/90
  - Football, 1990
  - Football, 1991
  - Football, 1992
  - Football, 1993
  - Football, 1994
  - Football, 1995
  - Football, 1996
  - Football, 1997
  - Football, 1998
  - Football, 1999
  - Football, 2000
  - Football, 2002
  - Football, 2003
  - Football, 2004
  - Football, 2006
  - Football, 2007
  - Football, 2008
  - Football, 2009
  - Football, 2011
  - Football, 2012
  - Football, 2013
  - Football, 2015
  - Football, 2016
  - Football, 2017
  - Football, 2019
  - Football, 2020
  - Football Concessions
  - Foote, Horton
  - Ford Foundation
  - Ford, Gerald
  - Ford Honors Program
  - Ford, Lester R.
  - Foreign Languages, Department of
  - [Rice U.] Foreign Language Program
  - [George R. Brown] Forensics Society
  - Formal Opening, 1912
  - Formal Opening, 1912 - Newsclips
  - Forman, Robin
  - For Rice's Honor (An evening for)
  - Forum on Global Competitiveness
  - Fossi, Margaret Everson
  - Fouke, Harry
  - Founder's Club
  - Founder's Day
  - Founder's Room
  - Founder's Society
  - Founder's Statue ("Willy's Statue")
  - Founder's Statue protests
  - [Henry S.] Fox Sr. Chair in Economics
  - [Gladys L.] Fox Chair in English
  - [Lena G.] Fox Chair in Political Science
  - [Henry and Lena] Fox Gymnasium
  - Fox, Stephen
  - Foyle, Kevin J.
  - Foyt Family Chair in Engineering
  - Francis, William H.
  - Francis, W. H., Jr.
  - Franck, Fance
  - Franco, Eusebio
  - Franklin, J.L., Jr.
  - Franzheim, Kenneth II
  - Fraser, Matt
  - Fredin, Leif
  - Freedmen's Town
  - Freeman, Carroll
  - Freeman, Charles Edward
  - Freeman, John W.
  - French and Italian, Dept. of
  - French Books
  - French Club
  - French Collection
  - French Commission for Public Affairs
  - French Mission Cavalier de la Salle
  - Freshman Dance, 1922
  - Freshman Initiation
  - Freshman Orientation
  - Freund, Max
  - Friar Tuck - In Service
  - Friday Night Underground
  - Friends of Rice
  - Friends of Rice Athletics
  - Friends of Rice Players
  - Friends of Rice Theater
  - Friendship Fund
  - Fuentes, Carlos
  - Fukuyama, Tohru
  - Fuller, R. Buckminster
  - Fulton, James S.
- Series VII: G
  - Gallant Harmon
  - Gallegly, Joseph S.
  - Gallop, Jane
  - Galveston
  - Gans, Herbert J.
  - Garcia, Caroline
  - Garcia, Jean-Pierre
  - Garcia, Jose (and mules)
  - Gardner, Gerald
  - Garfield, Lewis Edgar
  - [Houston] Gargoyle Magazine - Rice-related articles
  - Garrett, George
  - Garrett, Paula K.
  - Garside, Charles Jr.
  - Garwood, H.M.
  - [Rice] Gay & Lesbian Alumni Association
  - Gay/Lesbian Support Group
  - Geddes, Sir Auckland and Lady
  - Geddes Prize Essay Competition
  - Gene Hackerman Fund
  - Geographic Information Systems (GIS)/Data Center
  - Geology Building
  - Geology, Department of
  - George Foundation
  - Georges, Eugenia
  - German and Russian, Dept. of
  - German Club
  - German Federal State delegation visit
  - German Studies
  - Getcheroxoff
  - Geyer, Denton L.
  - Ghitalla, Armando
  - Ghorbel, Fathi
  - Ghosts on [Rice] campus
  - Gibbons, Reginald
  - Gibson, Brian
  - Gibson, Edward G.
  - Gifts
  - Giles, James B.
  - Gillan, Doug
  - Gille, Gaston
  - Gillis, Elizabeth
  - Gillis, Malcolm
  - Gillis, Malcolm - Articles by
  - Gillis, Malcolm - Biographical
  - Gillis, Malcolm - Inauguration
  - Gillis, Malcolm- Papers
  - Gillis, Malcolm - Speeches
  - Gilman, Susan K.
  - Gilmartin, Kristine
    See also: Wallace, Kristine Gilmartin
  - Gilruth, Robert R.
  - Girard, Andre Leon
  - Girard, Louis J.
  - Girls Rock Camp
  - [Campus] Girl Scouts
  - Giuliani, Rudolph
  - Glantz, Raymon M.
  - Glanville, James W.
  - Glascock, Clyde Chew
  - [Susanne M.] Glasscock School of Continuing Studies
  - Glass, Graham P.
  - Glee Club
  - Glendale Cemetery
  - Glenn, Jack
  - Glenwood Cemetery
    See also: Teich, Frank
  - Glick, William H.
  - Glidden, William H.
  - Global Urban Lab
  - Godwin Foundation
  - [Rice] Goethe Institute (now Goethe Center)
  - Golden Key National Honor Society
  - Golden Years
  - Goldsmith, Fred
  - Goldsmith, Kenneth
  - Goldston, Walter L.
  - Golf
  - Golf 1921/22 - 1946/47
  - Golson, William G.
  - Gomer, Richard H.
  - Gonzales, Alberto
  - Gonzales, Ruben
  - Goode, W.J.
  - Goodman, Charles M.
  - Goodman, Mary Ellen
  - Gorbachev, Mikhail
  - Gordon, Chad
  - Gordon, Richard G.
  - Gordon, William E.
    See also: Provost Records 1980-1985 (not in info files)
  - Gore, Al
  - Gorilla Girls
  - Gorman, Bridget
  - Gorry, G. Anthony
  - Goss, Warren E.
  - Gottschalk, Art
  - Gouge, Chris
  - Goundry, Paul Charles, Jr.
  - Goux, Jean-Joseph
  - Government Shutdown, Jan. 2019
  - Goyen, William
  - Grad News
  - Grades
  - Graduate House (now [Rice] Graduate Apartments)
  - Graduate Student Symposium on Literary Criticism
  - Graduate Symposium on Southern History
  - Graduate Study
  - Graduate Wives' Club
  - Graham Baker Studentship
  - Graham, Martin
  - Graham, Shad E.
  - Graham, Todd
  - Graham, Wayne
  - Grants
  - Graustein, William C.
  - Graves, John
  - Gray, Peter
  - Grayson, Marion L.
  - Greanias, George
    See also: Wilson, A Historical Play
  - Green Carbon Center
  - Green, Joan
  - Green, Oscar F.
  - Greene, Ann
  - Greene, Theodore M.
  - Greenspan, Alan
  - Greenspan, Rick
  - Gregory, Dick
  - Griffis, LeVan
  - Grigg, Cecil
  - Grob, Alan
  - Groundwater Research Center
  - Gruber, Ira
  - [Rice] Grubhound Team
  - Guadalajara, Mexico Trip, 1966
  - Guerard, Albert Joseph
  - Guerard, Albert Leon
    For articles, see faculty off-prints
  - Guerra, Rudy
  - Guertin, Ralph
  - Guggenheim Fellowship
  - Gulf Coast Consortia (GCC)
  - Gulf Coast Marine Sciences Center
  - Gulf Universities Research corporation
  - Gustin, Michael
  - Guthrie, David
  - Guy, Gawain
  - Gymnasium
    See also: [Henry and Lena] Fox Gymnasium; Autry Court
  - Gymnasium Air-Conditioning Project
- Series VIII: H
  - Habitat for Humanity (Rice Chapter)
  - HACER [Hispanic Association for Cultural Enrichment at Rice]
    See also: RAMAS; Tecolote
  - [Norman] Hackerman Award
  - [Gene and Norman] Hackerman Chair in History
  - Hackerman, Gene
  - Hackerman, Norman - Articles by
  - Hackerman, Norman - Awards, Honors
  - Hackerman, Norman - Biographical
  - Hackerman, Norman - Dinner
  - Hackerman, Norman - Inauguration
  - Hackerman, Norman - Inauguration Invitations
  - Hackerman, Norman - Interviews
  - Hackerman, Norman - Misc. Newsclippings
  - Hackerman, Norman - Move to Rice
  - Hackerman, Norman - Post-Inauguration
  - Hackerman, Norman - Speeches
  - HackRice
  - Hadamard, Jacques
  - Hafner, Jason
  - Hagan, Harold "Bo"
  - Halas, Naomi J.
  - Halberstam, David
  - Halbert, Martin
  - Hale, Elton B.
  - Hall, Arthur
  - Hall, David
  - Hall, Walter
  - Hallam, John S.
  - Halsey, Adm. William F. "Bull"
  - Hamburg David
  - Hamilton, Charles W.
  - Hamilton, Clayton
  - Hamilton, Larry
  - Hamilton, Mary Alice
  - Hamm, Keith E.
  - Hamman, George
  - Hamman Hall
  - Hammond, Brian R.
  - Hammond, Michael
  - Hamza, Maher "Mauro"
  - Hancock, David N.
  - Handshake
  - The Hangout
  - Hanks, Nancy
  - Hannah, Catherine
  - Hannah, David, Jr.
  - Hannon, James P.
  - Hansen, Fred
  - Hansz, Ingrid
  - Hanszen, Harry C.
  - Hapsburg, Otto Von
  - Harbison, E. Harris
  - HARC (Houston Area Research Center)
  - Harcombe, Paul
  - Harding Professorship in Mathematics
  - Hardt, Robert
  - Hardy, Joyce Pounds
  - Hardy, W.C. (Mr. and Mrs.)
  - Hargrove, James Ward
  - [Reginald H.] Hargrove Chair
  - Harlan Center
  - HARLiC
    See also: Houston Area Research Libraries Consortium
  - Harney, Paul
  - Harrell, Lynn
  - Harris, Brantley
  - Harris County Archives
  - Harris County Courthouse
  - Harris County-Houston Sports Authority
  - Harris County Settlers
  - Harris Gully
  - Harrison, Barbara
  - Harter, Deborah A.
  - Hartgerink, Jeffrey
  - Hartley, Peter R.
  - Hartshorne, Charles
  - Hartsook, Arthur
  - [A.J.] Hartsook Chair in Chemical Engineering
  - Harvey, F. Reese
  - Harvey, Shelly
  - [Marjory Meyer] Hasselmann Endowed Scholarship
  - Hassett, Brendan
  - Hatfield, Ken
  - Hauge, Robert
  - Havens, Neil
  - Haverkamp, Eva
  - Hawaii Bowl
  - Hawley, Richie
  - Hawthorne, Martha
  - Hayes, Edward F.
  - Haymes, Robert C.
  - Haynes, Fannie
  - Hayworth, Ronald
  - Hazing
  - Health and Physical Education, Dept. of
  - [Rice] Health Fair
  - [360] Health Initiative
  - Health Service
  - Health Violations
  - Heaps, Claude W.
  - Hebert, Joel
  - Hebl, Mikki
  - Hedlund, Ronald D.
  - Heisman, John
  - Hellums, Bonnie
  - Hellums, J. David
  - Helt, Richard C.
  - Hempel, Frieda
  - Hempel, John
  - Hendren, J.W.
  - Henry, Charles
  - Henstock, Tim
  - Henze, Matthais
  - H.E.R.E. Project
  - Heritage Society
  - Herman Brown Hall
    See also: [Hermann] Brown Hall for Mathematical Science
  - Herman Brown Park
  - Hermance, Gilbert L.
  - Hermann, George H.
  - Hermann Park
  - Herring, Robert Ray
  - [Robert R.] Herring Hall
  - Hertenberger, Lou
  - [Albert & Ethel] Herzstein Hall
    See also: Physics Building
  - Hess, Jake
  - Hess, Wilbur
  - Hester, Karen
  - Heyne, Roland
  - Hibben, John Grier
  - [Les] Hiboux
  - Hickey, Doralyn J.
  - Hicks, Marion
  - Higginbotham, S.W.
  - Hightower, Joseph W.
  - Hiles, Tom
  - Hill, Anita
  - Hill, Kim Quaile
  - Hill, King
  - Hill, Ross N.
  - Hill, Thomas W.
  - Hillel Organization
    See also: UA 343, Hillel T-Shirts
  - [Milus E.] Hindman Garden
  - Hines, Gerald Douglas
  - Hiraski, George
  - Hirschey, Mark
  - HISD/Rice School
  - Hispanic Heritage - Rice Events
  - Hispanic Professionals Leadership Day
  - Hispanic Studies, Dept. of
  - [Rice] Historical Marker
  - History and Political Science, Department of
  - Hitch, Arthur Romaine
  - Hjertberg, Earnest Winifred
  - Hoagland, Ray Watkin
    See also: Strange, Ray Watkin Hoagland
  - [William P.] Hobby Airport
  - [William P.] Hobby Chair in American History
  - Hobby, Diana
  - Hobby Family
  - Hobby Foundation
  - Hobby, Oveta C.
  - Hobby, William P., Jr.
  - Hochstettler, Tom
  - Hoffman, Abbie
  - Hoffman, Jeffrey A.
  - Hoffman, Marvin
  - Hogg, Will C.
  - Hohenthal Scholarship Fund
  - Hole, Frank
  - Holidays
  - Holland, John G.
  - Holloway, Edward & Naomi
  - Holocaust Museum
  - Holt, Edward
  - Homecoming, 1919
  - Homecoming, 1926
  - Homecoming, 1928
  - Homecoming, 1929
  - Homecoming, 1931
  - Homecoming, 1932
  - Homecoming, 1933
  - Homecoming, 1935
  - Homecoming, 1936
  - Homecoming, 1937
  - Homecoming, 1938
  - Homecoming, 1939
  - Homecoming, 1940
  - Homecoming, 1941
  - Homecoming, 1942
  - Homecoming, 1943
  - Homecoming, 1944
  - Homecoming, 1945
  - Homecoming, 1946
  - Homecoming, 1947
  - Homecoming, 1948
  - Homecoming, 1949
  - Homecoming, 1950
  - Homecoming, 1951
  - Homecoming, 1952
  - Homecoming, 1953
  - Homecoming, 1954
  - Homecoming, 1955
  - Homecoming, 1956
  - Homecoming, 1957
  - Homecoming, 1958
  - Homecoming, 1959
  - Homecoming, 1960
  - Homecoming, 1961
  - Homecoming, 1962
  - Homecoming, 1963
  - Homecoming, 1964
  - Homecoming, 1965
  - Homecoming, 1966
  - Homecoming, 1967
  - Homecoming, 1968
  - Homecoming, 1969
  - Homecoming, 1970
  - Homecoming, 1971
  - Homecoming, 1972
  - Homecoming, 1973
  - Homecoming, 1974
  - Homecoming, 1975
  - Homecoming, 1976
  - Homecoming, 1977
  - Homecoming, 1978
  - Homecoming, 1979
  - Homecoming, 1980
  - Homecoming, 1981
  - Homecoming, 1982
  - Homecoming, 1983
  - Homecoming, 1984
  - Homecoming, 1985
  - Homecoming, 1986
  - Homecoming, 1987
  - Homecoming, 1988
  - Homecoming, 1989
  - Homecoming, 1990
  - Homecoming, 1991
  - Homecoming, 1992
  - Homecoming, 1993
  - Homecoming, 1994
  - Homecoming, 1995
  - Homecoming, 1996
  - Homecoming, 1997
  - Homecoming, 1998
  - Homecoming, 1999
  - Homecoming, 2000
  - Homecoming, 2001
  - Homecoming, 2002
  - Homecoming, 2003
  - Homecoming, 2004
  - Homecoming, 2005
  - Homecoming, 2006
  - Homecoming, 2007
  - Homecoming, 2008
  - Homecoming, 2009
  - Homecoming, 2010
  - Homecoming, 2011
  - Homecoming, 2013
  - Homecoming, 2014
  - Homecoming, 2016
  - Homecoming
  - Homecoming, general
  - Honegger, Arthur
  - [President's] Honor Roll
  - [Rice] Honor System
  - Hood, Dorothy
  - Hood, Robert
  - The Hoot
  - Hooton, Claude
  - HOOTS (High Order of Owl Tailgate Society)
  - Hoover, Herbert
  - Hope, Bob
    See also: Jerry Lewis
  - [Rice] Housing and Dining (2 Folders)
    See also: [Rice] Food Service
  - Houston Archaeological Society
  - Houston Area Research Libraries Consortium (HARLiC)
  - Houston Area Survey
  - Houston Art League
  - Houston Ballet Guild
  - Houston Baptist University
  - Houston Bicycle Museum
  - Houston Blues Museum
  - Houston Club
  - Houston Community Shelter Plan, 1970
  - Houston Country Club
  - Houston Democratic National Convention, 1928
  - Houston Endowment Inc.
  - "Houston Engagement"
  - Houston Grand Opera Archives
  - Houston Fire Museum
  - Houston History
  - Houston Jewish History Archive
  - Houston Maritime Museum
  - Houston Metropolitan Research Center
  - Houston Public Library
  - Houston Rice Club
  - Houston, Sam
  - Houston Seminar
  - Houston Symphony Archives
  - Houston, William V.
  - Houston, William V. - Inauguration
  - Houston, William V. - Resignation and Death
  - Houston Yacht Club
  - Hovious, Brad
  - Howdy Week
  - Howell, Paul Nielson
  - Howell, William
  - Howton, William H.
  - Hoyle, Sir Fred
  - Huang, Huey W.
  - Hubbard, Laura
  - Hubbard, Molly
  - Hubble Telescope
  - Huberman, Brian